<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>

   <name>Email Signatures</name>
   <key>signatures</key>
   <state>stable</state>

   <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monta990/signatures/main/logo_small.png</logo>

   <description>
      <short>
         <en>Generate corporate PNG email signatures for your GLPI users.</en>
         <fr>Génère des signatures d'e-mail d'entreprise en PNG pour vos utilisateurs GLPI.</fr>
         <es>Genera firmas de correo corporativas en PNG para tus usuarios de GLPI.</es>
      </short>
      <long>
         <en><![CDATA[
Email Signatures generates personalized PNG email signature images for each GLPI user.
The signature includes full name, title, email address, phone numbers, Facebook page, corporate website and an optional WhatsApp QR code.

**Key features:**
- Two configurable PNG templates: one for users with a mobile number and one without.
- Dynamic image generation using PHP GD extension.
- Automatic font size adjustment to fit the user's name.
- WhatsApp QR code generated with TCPDF (bundled with GLPI).
- Send the signature directly to the user's email via GLPI's outgoing mail system.
- Dedicated tab on each user's profile with download and send buttons.
- Centralized configuration: templates, Facebook page, WhatsApp country code, email subject, body and footer.
- Visual drag-and-drop position editor per template — no PHP editing required.
- Live PNG preview before downloading or sending.
- Clickable variable badges (`{nombre}`, `{empresa}`, `{fecha}`) for quick insertion into email fields.
- Multilanguage: Spanish (Mexico), English (US), English (GB), French.
- Inline text formatting in email body and footer: `**bold**`, `*italic*`, `__underline__` with a one-click B/I/U toolbar. Styles are compatible with Outlook and Gmail.
- Compatible with GLPI 11.0+.
         ]]></en>
         <fr><![CDATA[
Email Signatures génère des images de signature d'e-mail PNG personnalisées pour chaque utilisateur GLPI.
La signature inclut le nom complet, le titre, l'adresse e-mail, les numéros de téléphone, la page Facebook, le site web et, en option, un code QR WhatsApp.

**Fonctionnalités principales :**
- Deux modèles PNG configurables : un pour les utilisateurs avec un numéro de portable et un sans.
- Génération dynamique via l'extension GD de PHP.
- Ajustement automatique de la taille de police pour le nom.
- Code QR WhatsApp généré avec TCPDF (inclus dans GLPI).
- Envoi de la signature via le système de courrier sortant de GLPI.
- Onglet dédié dans le profil de chaque utilisateur.
- Éditeur visuel de positions par glisser-déposer — sans modifier le PHP.
- Aperçu PNG avant téléchargement ou envoi.
- Multilingue : Español, English (US), English (GB), Français.
- Mise en forme dans le corps et le pied du mail : `**gras**`, `*italique*`, `__souligné__` avec une barre B/I/U. Styles inline compatibles avec Outlook et Gmail.
- Compatible avec GLPI 11.0+.
         ]]></fr>
         <es><![CDATA[
Email Signatures genera imágenes PNG personalizadas de firma de correo para cada usuario de GLPI.
La firma incluye nombre completo, título, correo, teléfonos, página de Facebook, sitio web y, opcionalmente, un código QR de WhatsApp.

**Características principales:**
- Dos plantillas PNG configurables: con o sin número celular.
- Generación dinámica sobre las plantillas usando la extensión GD de PHP.
- Ajuste automático del tamaño de fuente para el nombre del usuario.
- Código QR de WhatsApp generado con TCPDF (incluido en GLPI).
- Envío de la firma al correo del usuario mediante el sistema de correo saliente de GLPI.
- Pestaña dedicada en el perfil de cada usuario con botones de descarga y envío.
- Editor visual drag & drop de posiciones por plantilla — sin editar PHP.
- Vista previa del PNG antes de descargar o enviar.
- Variables insertables con un clic: `{nombre}`, `{empresa}`, `{fecha}`.
- Soporte multiidioma: Español (México), English (US), English (GB), Français.
- Formato de texto en el cuerpo y pie del correo: `**negrita**`, `*cursiva*`, `__subrayado__` con barra de herramientas B/I/U. Estilos inline compatibles con Outlook y Gmail.
- Compatible con GLPI 11.0+.
         ]]></es>
      </long>
   </description>

   <homepage>https://github.com/monta990/signatures</homepage>
   <download>https://github.com/monta990/signatures/releases</download>
   <issues>https://github.com/monta990/signatures/issues</issues>
   <readme>https://github.com/monta990/signatures/blob/main/README.md</readme>

   <authors>
      <author>Edwin Elias Alvarez (monta990)</author>
   </authors>

   <versions>

      <version>
         <num>1.3.3</num>
         <compatibility>~11.0.0</compatibility>
         <download_url>https://github.com/monta990/signatures/releases/download/1.3.3/signatures-1.3.3.zip</download_url>
      </version>

   </versions>

   <langs>
      <lang>es_MX</lang>
      <lang>en_US</lang>
      <lang>en_GB</lang>
      <lang>fr_FR</lang>
   </langs>

   <license>GPL v2+</license>

   <tags>
      <en>
         <tag>signature</tag>
         <tag>email</tag>
         <tag>png</tag>
         <tag>branding</tag>
      </en>
      <es>
         <tag>firma</tag>
         <tag>correo</tag>
         <tag>png</tag>
         <tag>branding</tag>
      </es>
      <fr>
         <tag>signature</tag>
         <tag>email</tag>
         <tag>png</tag>
         <tag>branding</tag>
      </fr>
   </tags>

   <screenshots>
      <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monta990/signatures/main/config.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monta990/signatures/main/user.png</screenshot>
   </screenshots>

</root>
